LILLIANN NABBAALE

0705744317 - nabbaalelilliann1996@gmail.com

Kampala, Uganda

Professional Summary

I am a highly resourceful, flexible, knowledgeable, and motivated individual with excellent communication skills both orally and written and pay greater attention to details in my work. My attention to detail and excellent time management skills means that every task is completed efficiently and to the highest possible standard. I have a calm and patient disposition meaning that I can work effectively under pressure and focus on the task at hand. I am proficient working in a team, but also work well independently. I am flexible, always focused and maintain a calm and professional demeanour, even when working under pressure. I am confident that with my skills and experience, I would make an excellent member of your team. I have excellent organization and communication skills meaning that I excel at leading a team and ensuring all assignments are completed on schedule. I am dedicated and keen to learn new skills to improve any experience for the benefit of me and the company that I work for. I am very keen to have a successful career. I am now looking forward to making a significant contribution to an institution that offers a genuine opportunity for progression.

Experience

Administrative Assistant

January 2021 to Current

Jolems Investment Ltd

While here, my role is to act as the point of contact for all staff Members and the Business Partners providing administrative support and managing their queries. My main duties include.

- Handling client correspondence and internal communications in a professional manner.
- Managing information on company databases for different organizational activities to track history and safeguard accurate information.
- Answering phones and performed clerical office functions to address queries, concerns, and issues, escalating complaints to management.
- Booking and paying for business travel and accommodation, communicating booking information to relevantstaff.
- Receiving, sorting and directing incoming mail to maintain good communication channels.
- Safeguarding sensitive and confidential data in compliance with security best practices.
- Planning office events by reserving venues, communicating schedules and coordinating set up.
- Receiving all mails, recording, and ensuring they are dispatched to the authorized staff.
- Updating and coordinating the calendar of our company to ensure timely achievement of our goals.

Administrative Officer

January 2020 to December 2020

Inside Out Logistics

- Coordinated communications between various departments to schedule meetings and keep company informed on critical matters.
- Provided overall leadership and supervision to all the staff.
- · Received company documents and ensured they are captured and filed to ensure their safety.
- Maintained staff welfare, by ensuring they take their leaves where necessary.
- Purchased office supplies every month and monitoring their utilization to update the inventory.
- Directed incoming mail, interoffice messages, and packages to office recipients.
- Kept office operations running smoothly and efficiently by implementing procedure and policyimprovements.

Administrator

January 2019 to December 2019

Covermark Ltd

While here, I oversaw, answering phones, scheduling appointments, and maintaining calendars, scheduling and coordinating staff and other meetings, collating and distributing mail and preparing communications, such as memos, emails, invoices, reports and other correspondences.

- Ensured efficient space planning by enabling a productive and comfortable working environment, make a certain that the office is clean and accommodative. This promoted collaboration and efficiency in the office.
- Maintained phones, managed calendars, scheduled appointments, luncheons and conference calls, mail handling and visitor management thus creating a welcoming and organized office environment.
- Organized the office and designed systems to maximize administrative operations.
- Arranged and maintained sensitive documents in compliance with security procedures.

Trainee

June 2018 to August 2018

Uganda Revenue Authority

- While here, my role was to participate in the records keeping process of the Organization to ensure timely retrieval documents.
- Received, acknowledged, and recorded documents from different departments.
- Captured the documents in the database system.
- Filed the documents for safety, timely access and storing them.
- Retrieved documents when an authorized staff needed them for reference.
- Identified space, prepared location numbers, and pasted them on the transferred records.

Core Qualifications

- Prudent & result oriented.
- Proficient communication & organization skills.
- · Customer care skills.

- Organization and efficiency
- Computer Literacy. Comfortable with Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point, and Outlook.
- Interpersonal, proactive and team player.

Education

Bachelor of Office and Information Management, 2020

Makerere University Business School - Kampala

Uganda Certificate of Education (UACE), 2015

St. Mary's Kitende - Kampala

Uganda Certificate of Education (UCE), 2013

St. Augstine's college Wakiso - Kampala

References

1. Name: Badru Bukenya Phd

Position: Professor

Organization: Makerere University

Email: badrub@gmail.com

Mobile: +256 701393250 / +256 788889804

Name: Charles Ssegane Position: Deputy Manager

Organisation: Jubilee Allianz General Insurance

Email: charles.ssegane@allianz.com Mobile +256 773352566 / +256 700852261

3. Name: Jolems Mwanje Position: Managing Director

Organisation: Jolems Investment Limited

Email: md@jolemsproducts.com

Mobile: +256 709295211

Languages

English: Excellent in speaking, reading & writing

· Luganda: Excellent in speaking, reading & writing

Hobbies

Exploring & travelling.

· Discussion.